<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DZ1</string>
    <string name="barbara_liskov">
        Barbara Liskov\n07.10.1939. -\nBarbara Liskov is an American computer scientist and an Institute Professor at the Massachusetts
        Institute of Technology. She was one of the first women to be granted a doctorate in computer science in the United States and
        is a Turing Award winner who developed the Liskov substitution principle.
    </string>

    <string name="john_resig">John Resig\n08.05.1983. -\nJohn Resig is an American software engineer and entrepreneur, best known as the creator and lead
        developer of the jQuery JavaScript library.currently works as an application developer at Khan Academy. Previously, he was a JavaScript
        tool developer for the Mozilla Corporation.
    </string>

    <string name="grace_hopper">
        Grace Hopper\n09.12.1906. - 01.01.1992.\nGrace Brewster Murray Hopper was an American computer scientist and United States Navy rear admiral.
        One of the first programmers of the Harvard Mark I computer, she was a pioneer of computer programming who invented one of the first compiler
        related tools. She popularized the idea of machine-independent programming languages, which led to the development of COBOL.

    </string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome!</string>

    <string-array name="barbara_quotes">
        <item>I didn\'t have a plan for where I was going. Instead I reacted to obstacles and opportunities.</item>
        <item>Be aware of what you\’re doing, and what the opportunities are, and step into what seems right, and see where it takes you.</item>
        <item>Figure out what you like to do, and what you can do well—and the two are not all that dissimilar, because you don\’t typically like
            doing something if you don’t do it well.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="john_quotes">
        <item>Write code every day.</item>
        <item>Technology in-and-of itself doesn\'t solve anything. You have to understand the people and the problems and fix the processes at the
            core in order to make improvement.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="grace_quotes">
        <item>Some day, on the corporate balance sheet, there will be an entry which reads, \"Information\"; for in most cases,
            the information is more valuable than the hardware which processes it.</item>
        <item>The only phrase I\'ve ever disliked is, \'Why, we\'ve always done it that way.\' I always tell young people,
            \'Go ahead and do it. You can always apologize later.\'</item>
        <item>Humans are allergic to change. They love to say, \'We\'ve always done it this way.\' I try to fight that.
            That\'s why I have a clock on my wall that runs counter-clockwise.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
